chew
嚼
Your test is complete
您的测试已完成
Hold on
稍等
what's the result?
结果是什么？
no problem
没问题
Then I'll prepare her for the next exam
然后我会让她准备下一次考试
Yes
是的
Your basic information and medical examination report
您的基本信息和体检报告
I've seen it all
我都看过了
They are all excellent
他们都很优秀
Next is the actual case
接下来是实际案例
This man's son
这个人的儿子
This is the robot Ming investigated last week.
这是明某上周调查的机器人。
Men are busy at work
男人们都忙于工作
Out of town all year round
常年在城外
until my son was born
直到儿子出生
There is no time to go back to accompany the childbirth
没有时间回去陪产
feel guilty
感到内疚
So to his wife
所以对他的妻子
This is the only son
这是唯一的儿子
i really love you
我真的很爱你
presumptuous
放肆
I said it a while ago
我前阵子说过
He couldn't even be with his son when he was born.
连儿子出生时他都无法陪伴。
But his son was not investigated and the matter was discovered
但他的儿子没有被调查，事情就被发现了
Is it a robot?
它是机器人吗？
In fact, his son was just born
事实上，他的儿子刚刚出生
go to hell
去死吧
It's because of my wife's negligence
正是因为妻子的疏忽
his wife hid this
他的妻子隐瞒了这一点
He bought this robot when he was a kid
他小时候买了这个机器人
What if his son is an Android?
他的儿子是安卓怎么办？
How was he identified?
他是如何被识别出来的？
My wife took the kids out last week
上周我妻子带着孩子们出去了
I had an accident
我出了车祸
This thing was just discovered
这东西刚刚被发现
Everyone passed the first round of assessment.
大家都通过了第一轮考核。
Excellent talents
优秀人才
What we need to do now is
我们现在需要做的是
Try not to arouse his emotions
尽量不引起他的情绪
let him know everything
让他知道全部事情
Do you have any good ideas?
你有什么好主意吗？
his wife
他的老婆
Where are you now?
你现在在哪里？
in hospital
在医院
Coma for several days
昏迷数日
I just woke up last night
我昨晚刚醒
Start when you're ready
准备好后即可开始
Wanbo, let me go first
万博，让我先走
Help yourself
帮助自己
Mr. Fang
方先生
I think it should be used a lot
我认为它应该被大量使用
more exciting way
更令人兴奋的方式
How do you do it?
你怎么做呢？
I just want to
只是想
if i were him
如果我是他
What would I think now?
我现在会怎么想？
The average person’s first reaction
一般人的第一反应
maybe angry
也许生气
He hates his wife for killing his son
他恨他的妻子杀了他的儿子
I also purchased an Android device
我还购买了 Android 设备
you want to hide errors
你想隐藏错误
I told him
我告诉他了
Compared to his hatred
相比于他的仇恨
Maybe his wife hates him more.
也许他的妻子更讨厌自己。
She lives with the pain of losing her son
她生活在失去儿子的痛苦之中
Living with the guilt of betraying her husband
带着背叛丈夫的愧疚生活
nobody
没有人
More painful than a mother losing her child
比失去孩子的母亲还要痛苦
But she chose to bear it all
但她选择承受这一切
She doesn't want the family to break up
她不想让家庭破裂
That's why she bought the robot
这就是她买机器人的原因
despite losing his son
尽管失去了儿子
But he has another one
但他还有一个
deeply in love with his wife
深深地爱着他的妻子
That's it
就是这样
chew
嚼
you did a great job today
你今天干得很好
I'm surprised
我很惊讶
Why do you think of traumatized people?
你为什么会想到受过创伤的人？
So got it
所以明白了
I just want to put myself in other people's shoes.
我只是想设身处地为别人着想
to be honest
说实话
years ago
几年前
My family has also undergone some changes
我的家庭也发生了一些变化
so far
迄今为止
I'm still learning how to face it
我还在学习如何面对
what did you just say?
你刚刚说什么？
it gave me a lot of ideas
它给了我很多想法
Thanks
谢谢
Welcome to Mingmou
欢迎加入明谋
Why don't you turn on the light?
你为什么不开灯？
How is the investigation going?
调查情况如何？
Come
来
this is your seat
这是你的座位
he proposes
他提出
chew
嚼
I have already met
我已经遇见了
starting today
从今天开始
She is your new partner
她是你的新搭档
welcome
欢迎
you know each other
你们互相认识
Get started quickly
快速上手
minister
部长
I think it's about Chen Xinhui
我觉得是陈新辉的事
There are still many doubts
仍有很多疑点
How to say
怎么说
After the murderer killed Qin Xinhui
凶手杀死秦新辉后
The scene is carefully arranged
场景经过精心布置
This sense of ritual
这种仪式感
like a signature
就像签名一样
I don't think he just wants to please
我认为他不只是想取悦
pleasure of killing
杀人的快感
More like a psychological need
更像是一种心理需求
So I think
所以我认为
There must be another murder
一定还有另一起谋杀案
serial murder case
连环杀人案
He left such a pattern at the scene
他在现场留下了这样的图案
it must express something
它必须表达一些东西
Cheng Nu
程女
what do you think
你怎么认为
What does this have to do with us?
这和我们有什么关系呢？
serial murder case
连环杀人案
Of course it has nothing to do with us
当然与我们无关
But if the murderer only kills androids
但如果凶手只杀仿生人
That nature is different
那性质就不一样了
this killer
这个杀手
As a result, Shen Li was still lying on the hospital bed.
结果，沉黎还躺在病床上。
Don't you want to catch him?
你不想抓住他吗？
I forgot
我忘了
It was you who made Shen Li lie on the hospital bed.
是你让沉丽躺在病床上的。
serial murder case
连环杀人案
You must match at least three victims
您必须匹配至少三个受害者
Where is the evidence?
证据在哪里？
i will find her
我会找到她
Yes
是的
when
什么时候
Well, of course we need to find evidence.
嗯，我们当然需要找到证据。
But I also couldn't give up on the problem at hand.
但我也不能放弃手头的问题。
Get along well with your new partner
与你的新伙伴相处融洽
Is this a new topic of investigation?
这是一个新的调查课题吗？
What does she have to do with you?
她跟你有什么关系？
I do it myself
我自己做
You don't know, do you?
你不知道，是吗？
About the evaluation report
关于评估报告
Requires signatures of two investigators
需要两名调查员签名
that is
就是说
if i don't sign
如果我不签名
you can't do anything
你什么也做不了
Don't want to see it? Go check it out.
不想看吗？去看看吧。
golden flame
金色火焰
sculpture
雕塑
shattered
破碎的
Is this Cheng Nuo's new suspect?
这是程诺的新嫌疑人吗？
Stars shine in the lonely night
星星在孤独的夜里闪耀
I see you sleeping soundly next to me
我看到你在我旁边睡得很香
I slept peacefully without any pain in my heart
我睡得很安稳，心里没有任何痛苦
I feel like I'm right next to you
我感觉我就在你身边
The breeze whispers on the bright day
微风在明亮的日子里低语
You are the one who lights me up with your smile
你是用你的微笑照亮我的人
you are My Sunshine
你是我的阳光
sorry
对不起
I didn't see anyone coming
我没看到有人来
You're here too early, aren't you?
你来得太早了，不是吗？
no no
不，不
Let me get you a glass of water first
我先给你倒杯水
Thanks
谢谢
This is the wine list
这是酒单
I want this
我要这个
Now that song
现在那首歌
Singing is nice
唱歌很好听
Thank you so much
非常感谢
Actually this song
其实这首歌
my favorite wife
我最喜欢的妻子
When I have nothing to do, I practice secretly
没事的时候我就偷偷练习
See when there is a chance
看看什么时候有机会
Just sing to her
就唱歌给她听
very romantic
很浪漫
this sculpture
这个雕塑
Is this the work of Jin Yan?
这是金焰的作品吗？
you know her
你认识她
i really love her
我真的很爱她
Very powerful artist
很有实力的艺人
Yes
是的
I have many of her sculptures in my shop
我的店里有很多她的雕塑
this
这
there there
那里那里
Everyone has a different opinion on sculpture
每个人对雕塑都有不同的看法
What do you think?
你觉得这怎么样？
I guess
我猜测
Sounds like someone is struggling
听起来有人在挣扎
Yes
是的
my thoughts
我的想法
looks very comfortable
看起来很舒服
Boss, do you know Jin Yan?
老大，你认识金燕吗？
we know each other
我们互相认识
She also has a stake in the store
她也有这家店的股份
So what kind of person is she?
那么她是一个什么样的人呢？
she
她
she is a good person
她是一个好人
if you want anything else
如果你还想要什么
tell me
告诉我
Come on, come on, the car is coming, I'm coming
来来来，车来了，我来
I won't go, I really won't go.
我不去，真的不去。
It's okay, I'll take you there
没关系，我带你去
presentable
体面的
I told you I'm tired
我告诉过你我累了
I want to go home and then I'll take you there
我想回家，然后我带你去
There is no need for me to come back in person.
我没有必要亲自回来。
this is my friend
这是我的朋友
I'll give it to you
我就把它交给你
Thanks
谢谢
you are your friend
你是你的朋友
Yes
是的
Yes, yes, my friend
是的，是的，我的朋友
goodbye
再见
Be careful next time you are alone
下次你一个人的时候要小心
Thanks
谢谢
she
她
she is a good person
她是一个好人
miss
错过
Sorry, we don't start until tomorrow
抱歉，我们明天才开始
tomorrow
明天
correct
正确的
Then I remembered the wrong date
然后我记错日期了
But I like Teacher Jin Yan very much
不过我很喜欢金燕老师
I came from somewhere else specifically
我是特地从别的地方来的
he came here
他来到这里
Can I take a look in advance?
我可以提前看一下吗？
please
请
Okay, okay, okay
好吧好吧好吧
Thank you for showing me around
谢谢你带我四处参观
Master Jin Yan has painted before.
金炎大师以前画过。
Yes, but that was in the early days
是的，不过那是早期的事了
She hasn't painted for a long time
她已经很久没有画画了
let me show you this
让我给你看看这个
This is called liberation
这就是所谓的解脱
When teacher Jin Yan designed
金燕老师设计时
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
I guess
我猜测
It is the pursuit of a kind of incomplete beauty
是对一种残缺之美的追求
I believe love and honesty are inseparable
我相信爱和诚实是密不可分的
Honesty means honesty and sincerity
诚实意味着诚实和真诚
sincerely
真心实意
It also represents our hearts
也代表了我们的心
Who is this?
这是谁？
This is Kim Gwan Sook’s sister’s husband
这是金官淑姐姐的丈夫
Two famous rock songs are Justin Bieber and Hilary Duff
两首著名的摇滚歌曲是贾斯汀·比伯和希拉里·达芙
That's what it looks like
看起来就是这样
Come here and show me this
过来给我看看这个
This all happened two years ago
这一切都发生在两年前
Hello sir what do you need?
您好先生您需要什么？
Americano
美式咖啡
Yes
是的
What a coincidence
真是巧合
thank you yesterday
昨天谢谢你
He should
他应该
I'll buy you a drink
我请你喝一杯
Hello, two glasses of red wine
你好，两杯红酒
Why do you drink so much every time?
为什么每次都喝那么多？
One cup after another
一杯接着一杯
just drunk
刚刚喝醉了
you don't have any worries
你没有任何担忧
What questions do you have?
您有什么问题？
life's work
一生的工作
marriage
婚姻
you are married.
你结婚了。
Very annoying
很烦人
And she doesn't wear the ring anymore
而且她不再戴戒指了
Yes
是的
you don't want to wear it
你不想穿它
bondage
束缚
clear
明白
You hate him so much
你太恨他了
So why not divorce?
那为什么不离婚呢？
Are you interested in my husband?
你对我丈夫很感兴趣吗？
No
不
just me
只有我
Wondering why it makes you angry
想知道为什么它让你生气
To prevent yourself from entering a minefield?
为了避免自己进入雷区？
Okay, stop talking about me
好了，别再谈论我了
Please introduce yourself
介绍一下你自己吧
What's your job
你做什么工作
warn
警告
thank you for taking me home
谢谢你带我回家
I am happy today
我今天很开心
I'm glad too
我也很高兴
This is my home
这是我的家
it arrived
它到达了
OK
好的
you must remember
你必须记住
I will remember
我会记住的
Be careful
当心
Hello
你好
here we go again
又来了
Come on, come on, hello, hello
来来来，你好，你好
any drink
任何饮料
Just like you
和你一样
I went to see Jin Yan’s exhibition
我去看了金燕的展览
I saw a picture of the two of you together.
我看到你们两个在一起的照片
she is your wife
她是你的妻子
I didn't tell you yesterday
我昨天没告诉你
because
因为
She doesn't like me and others very much
她不太喜欢我和其他人
talk about us
谈论我们
Do you know the artist?
你了解艺术家吗？
her lifestyle
她的生活方式
Are you very different from ordinary people?
你和常人有很大不同吗？
Not much different, right?
没什么不同，对吧？
I like it very much
我非常喜欢它
when it works
当它起作用时
The mystery it brings to me
它给我带来的神秘感
your ring
你的戒指
Looks good, doesn't it?
看起来不错，不是吗？
she did
她做过
Do you care about her?
你关心她吗？
hey this is me
嘿，这就是我
take it with you
带上它
stop talking about me
别再谈论我了
Today is my everything
今天是我的全部
sorry for your excuse
对不起你的借口
Sit anywhere
随便坐
The second floor I just passed
我刚经过的二楼
Is this your studio?
这是你的工作室吗？
I am very interested
我很感兴趣
How about we go take a look?
我们去看看怎么样？
you came here to drink
你来这里是为了喝酒
I don't like people coming to my studio
我不喜欢人们来到我的工作室
Let's drink first
我们先喝
what to do
应该做什么
hurry up
快点
i still believe
我仍然相信
you are so weird
你太奇怪了
You're in a good mood, aren't you?
你心情很好，不是吗？
Are you really not angry?
你真的不生气吗？
He still can't be angry
他还是没办法生气
do you know
你知道吗
That's exactly how you reacted.
你的反应确实是这样的。
What's that called?
那叫什么？
Android
安卓
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
he is my husband
他是我的丈夫
this is marriage
这就是婚姻
After a long time, there is no passion anymore
时间长了就没有激情了
That's why we have to be outside
这就是为什么我们必须在外面
looking for some excitement
寻找一些刺激
Is it true, my husband?
是真的吗，我的丈夫？
Yes
是的
Don't you think so?
你不这么认为吗
He is really obedient
他真的很听话
Yes or no
是还是不是
You cannot go against your original obsession.
你无法违背自己最初的执念。
I don't know what you're talking about, come on
我不知道你在说什么，快点
Where is the real sequence?
真正的序列在哪里？
what have you done? did you hurt me?
你做了什么？你伤害了我吗？
let her go
让她走
Cheng Nu
程女
Who are you?
你是谁？
If you don't leave, I'll call the police
你再不走我就报警了
Cheng Nu
程女
You knew the problem was Guan Xu from the beginning
你从一开始就知道问题出在关旭身上
why don't you tell me
你为什么不告诉我
Doesn't this give you a chance?
这不给你机会吗？
How do you think you left your bar card?
您认为您是如何留下酒吧名片的？
the result of doing this
这样做的结果
What was found?
发现了什么？
Why didn't she put in so much effort to fall in love with Jin Yan?
她为什么不费这么大劲去跟靳言谈恋爱呢？
And then you get nothing?
然后你什么也没得到？
Not really, right?
不完全是，对吧？
he saw one
他看到了一个
The robot’s mind is full of love and motivation
机器人满脑子都是爱，充满动力
Isn't this interesting?
这不是很有趣吗？
What have you been through?
你经历了什么？
There is a lot of hostility towards robots
对机器人有很多敌意
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
The fact that Guan Xu is a robot
关旭是机器人的事实
It's a sure thing
确实是确定的事
Where is the evidence?
证据在哪里？
Without evidence, you've exposed your trump card.
没有证据，你就暴露了你的底牌。
You have alerted the enemy
你已经惊动了敌人
lack of experience
缺乏经验
What did you say
你说什么
Feed the Gu team
喂顾队
Because of your problem, I would like to contact the police.
由于您的问题，我想联系警方。
Address: No. 77 Huayuan Road
地址：花园路77号
Emergency situations
紧急情况
I will come back to report on the status of the order
我会回来报告订单情况
OK
好的
what do you want to do?
你想让我做什么？
do not move
别动
pain
疼痛
No pain
不痛
Thanks
谢谢
don't say anything
不要说什么
We'll pack our bags later
我们稍后收拾行李
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Buy ferry tickets
购买渡轮票
It's not too late
现在还不算太晚
It's a burglary, you know?
这是入室盗窃，你知道吗？
Look, they're really leaving
看，他们真的要走了
he goes
他走
Not much, not much, buy it later.
不多了，不多了，以后再买吧。
I just came here
我刚来这里
Her eyes keep escaping
她的目光一直在逃避
This means there must be a ghost here
这意味着这里一定有鬼
One look makes you so sure
一看就让你如此确定
fully understand women
充分了解女性
I am a professional
我是专业人士
The job is still for women
工作依然是女人
Hold on
稍等
I'll go get something from the second floor
我去二楼拿点东西
come over
过来
main
主要的
very worried
非常担心
where are you going?
你要去哪里？
Where is your husband?
你的丈夫呢？
Where are the others?
其他人在哪里？
I have no idea
我不知道
We broke up two years ago
我们两年前分手了
What was the reason for the breakup?
分手的原因是什么？
As time goes by, feelings will fade
随着时间的推移，感情会淡化
Then since the feelings gradually faded away
然后自从感情渐渐淡去
Why did you buy another one?
你为什么又买了一件？
Robot sequences look very similar
机器人序列看起来非常相似
I'm a whore myself
我自己就是个妓女
I still have feelings for him
我对他还是有感情的
Where are you right now so worried about where you want to go?
你现在在哪里如此担心你想去哪里？
my wife wants to travel
我的妻子想去旅行
Night flights are cheaper
夜间航班更便宜
wife
妻子
You are just a robot she bought
你只是她买来的机器人
Do you really think you are her husband?
你真以为你是她老公吗？
What's with the blood in your studio?
你工作室里的血迹是怎么回事？
I have no idea
我不知道
This is your last chance to tell the truth
这是你说实话的最后机会
What happened two years ago?
两年前发生了什么？
According to our poll
根据我们的民意调查
Before the real Guan Xu disappears
在真正的关旭消失之前
Jin Yan has suffered from domestic violence for a long time
金燕长期遭受家庭暴力
We strongly suspect she is distraught
我们强烈怀疑她心烦意乱
So she attacked her husband
于是她袭击了她的丈夫
hide what you do
隐藏你所做的事
I just bought you as camo
我只是买了你作为迷彩
No clue?
没有线索吗？
And the evidence I said
还有我说的证据
Our police will definitely find it
我们警察一定会找到的
under any circumstances
任何状况之下
Your wife is now the biggest suspect
你老婆现在是最大的嫌疑人
promising artist
有前途的艺术家
Kill husband and abandon body
杀夫弃尸
I think this should be big news
我觉得这应该是个大新闻
Do you think she can still survive in this circle?
你觉得她还能在这个圈子里生存吗？
Will you survive?
你能活下来吗？
Jin Yan and Guan Shuo have been separated for a long time
金燕和关硕已经分开很久了
when i got home that day
那天我回到家时
he is there too
他也在那儿
I'm back
我回来了
from?
从？
Jin Yan really made one
金燕真的做了一个
Exactly the same as me
和我一模一样
excuse me
打扰一下
How should I address you as?
我应该怎么称呼你？
Come here and let me see
过来让我看看
It's really done.
真的完成了。
Do you look like me?
你看起来像我吗？
Nothing like it
一点也不像
What's your job
你做什么工作
are you a man?
你是个男人吗？
What do you do
你是做什么的
I tell you
我告诉你
you
你
It’s just that Jin Yan is like me and your master
只是金言就像我和你师父
customized product
定制产品
you can never replace me
你永远无法取代我
What's your job
你做什么工作
do not move
别动
I am alone
我是一个人
you are a dog
你是一条狗
you are talking nonsense
你在胡说八道
Jin Yan is tired of playing with you
金燕跟你玩腻了
he will throw you away
他会把你扔掉
When
到时
you are just a stray dog
你只是一只流浪狗
What's the dog's name?
狗叫什么？
call sir
打电话给先生
Jin Yan, come here
金燕你过来
Play with your dog with me
和我一起玩你的狗
prostitute
妓女
golden flame
金色火焰
Play with me, your dog
和我一起玩吧，你的狗
Jin Yan, come here
金燕你过来
you are a poor woman
你是个可怜的女人
prostitute
妓女
What do you like about inflatable dolls?
你对充气娃娃有怎样的喜爱？
Jin Yan, come here
金燕你过来
golden flame
金色火焰
go out
出去
The robot surrendered
机器人投降了
OK! I already know
好的！我已经明白了
you can leave now
你现在可以离开了
Don’t leave Saiyuan City yet
暂时不要离开西原城
presumptuous
放肆
You have to go back and educate this child properly.
你得回去好好教育这个孩子。
Yes
是的
Well, that's it.
好吧，就这样吧。
elder sister
姐姐
You have time to climb the wall
你有时间爬墙
You don't have time to treat me to dinner, do you?
你没有时间请我吃饭，是吗？
You still have this with you
你还带着这个
Onkyo Onkyo Onkyo
安桥 安桥 安桥
chew
嚼
break into private residence
闯入私人住宅
Are you cool now?
你现在酷吗？
chew
嚼
Stay away from Qingnv from now on
从此远离青女
Do something illegal and unregulated
做一些非法和不受监管的事情
remember?
记住？
he feels sorry
他感到抱歉
Go, go, go, walk quickly
走走走快走
Thank you, Team Gu
谢谢顾队
Kaneko
金子
all
全部
Are you familiar with it?
你熟悉吗？
This sister
这位姐姐
It's the Gu team of the Ministry of Public Security detachment.
是公安部支队顾队。
About all Android cases of Mingmou
关于明谋所有Android案例
Just to communicate with her
只是为了和她沟通
you killed that man
你杀了那个人
Jin Yan doesn’t know anything
金妍什么都不知道
Where is the body?
尸体在哪里？
The body is under the statue
尸体在雕像下方
Hold on
稍等
ETC。
ETC。
This is what Guan Xu asked me to give you.
这是关旭让我给你的。
He said he saved it for you
他说他是为你保存的
I'll give it back to you now
我现在还给你
Now that he admits it
既然他承认了
The case is considered closed.
此案被视为结案。
This is the current result
这是现在的结果
Maybe you feel bad too
也许你也感觉不好
For someone who's not even a real person
对于一个甚至不是一个真实的人的人
The robot is sad
机器人很伤心
this is unreasonable
这是不合理的
not a real person
不是真实的人
all the time
每时每刻
What do you think the current situation is?
您认为目前的情况是？
This is a false existence
这是一个虚假的存在
That's why you doubt
这就是你怀疑的原因
Does he really love you?
他真的爱你吗？
Then I want to ask
那我想问一下
What criteria do you use?
您使用什么标准？
determine their health status
判断其健康状况
Is he really off the hook?
他真的摆脱困境了吗？
still
仍然
Does he really love you?
他真的爱你吗？
How do you feel about him?
你对他感觉如何？
Do you love him
你爱他吗
Ms. Kim
金女士
the feelings between you
你们之间的感情
I am not qualified to comment
我没有资格评论
but i think
但我觉得
Only people who do wrong things
只有做错事的人
need to take responsibility
需要承担责任
Take care of yourself
保重
Ms. Jane thanks you for your cooperation
简女士感谢您的合作
Let's go first
我们先走吧
all the time
每时每刻
What do you think the current situation is?
您认为目前的情况是？
This is a false existence
这是一个虚假的存在
That's why you doubt
这就是你怀疑的原因
Does he really love you?
他真的爱你吗？
Do you know the more of you the better for me?
你知道你越多对我越好吗？
The more I feel
我越觉得
I feel like I can't breathe
我感觉我无法呼吸
I'm grateful for everything you've done for me
我很感激你为我所做的一切
But why don't you understand?
但你为什么不明白呢？
i can't fall in love with you
我无法爱上你
So I'm sad too
所以我也很难过
What you need is a
你需要的是一个
Someone who can love you too
一个也可以爱你的人
not me
不是我
Why isn't one enough?
为什么一个还不够？
I want to withdraw from him
我想从他身边退出
I don't need money
我不需要钱
But you have to help me find a good home for him
但你得帮我给他找一个好归宿
If the item was not custom made for you, who should I return it to?
如果不是为您定制的商品，我应该将其退回给谁？
And, no one is going to take over this product.
而且，没有人会接管这个产品。
you more or less
你或多或少
Why don't you give me some processing fee?
为什么不给我一些处理费？
How much do you want?
你想要多少？
birthday present
生日礼物
Give me
给我
Mother
母亲
president
总统
Where did you sell it?
你在哪里卖的？
Why are the conditions so bad?
为什么条件这么差？
This condition is limited
这个条件是有限的
Who buys these now?
现在谁还买这些？
Uncustomized robot
未定制的机器人
It's all customized to your requirements
这一切都是根据您的要求定制的
Do you still want it?
你还想要吗？
Count money
数钱
What’s wrong with you
你怎么了
Did I do something wrong again?
难道我又做错事了？
I apologize to you, I'm sorry.
我向你道歉，对不起。
Can I really go with you?
我真的可以和你一起去吗？
if i go with you
如果我和你一起去
Will you feel better?
你会感觉好一点吗？
If you don't leave, I will leave
你若不走，我便离开
Is it made for just the two of us?
是为我们两个人做的吗？
can i try
我可以试试吗
Yes
是的
You are done polishing
您已完成抛光
correct
正确的
You can use more power here
您可以在这里使用更多电量
What kind of person is he?
他是一个什么样的人？
Then it
那它
he will hurt me
他会伤害我
people who don't believe me
不相信我的人
What's your job
你做什么工作
too late
太晚了
Just don't come back
只是不要回来
What if I find out?
如果我发现了怎么办？
She tells you that she is on a business trip.
她告诉你她正在出差。
very beautiful
很漂亮
If not beautiful
不漂亮的话
Why do you want to model nude for your wife?
你为什么想为你的妻子做裸体模特？
But I think her paintings
但我觉得她的画
I really haven’t drawn your beauty yet
我真的还没画出你的美
wife
妻子
Why did you come back?
你为什么回来？
listen to me
听我说
this is not what you see
这不是你所看到的
She really came here on her own initiative
她真的是主动来到这里的
i apologize to you
我向你道歉
I'm really sorry
实在抱歉
you go
你去
I don't want to see you again
我不想再见到你
Don't do this, I apologize.
不要这样做，我向你道歉
Do not touch me
不要碰我
You are listening to my explanation
你在听我的解释
I think you are disgusting
我觉得你很恶心
That's really not what you see
这真的不是你所看到的
Well, you're not leaving, are you?
好吧，你不会离开，是吗？
If you don't leave, I will leave
你若不走，我便离开
Okay, okay, okay
好吧好吧好吧
ok i don't feel good
好吧，我感觉不舒服
Can't I apologize to you?
我不能向你道歉吗？
do not leave
不要离开
Come on, come in and tell me
来吧，进来告诉我
Do you think this is just my problem?
你认为这只是我的问题吗？
You draw every day
你每天都会画画
make your statue
制作你的雕像
Have you ever thought about what I want?
你有没有想过我想要什么？
Let me go
让我走
all
全部
Now we're even
现在我们扯平了
Don't be angry, okay?
别生气，好吗？
I love you
我爱你
I only love you, please leave
我只爱你，请你离开
Stop fighting, okay? Let me go
别再打架了，好吗？让我走
Are you done?
你完成了吗？
Did you finish it?
你做完了吗？
Can I give you face?
我给你面子好不好？
you are done
你完成了
I love you
我爱你
I beg you, please stop making trouble.
我求求你，别再闹了。
wife
妻子
I'm different from him
我和他不一样
I will never hurt you
我永远不会伤害你
you killed that man
你杀了那个人
Jin Yan doesn’t know anything
金妍什么都不知道
sorry
对不起
I always owe you an apology
我一直欠你一个道歉
these two years
这两年
I am every moment
我在每时每刻
Everyone feels uncomfortable
大家都感觉不舒服
Whenever you want me to be happy
每当你希望我快乐的时候
the more guilty you feel
你越感到内疚
The more I feel sorry
越觉得遗憾
But I'm more afraid of falling in love with you
但我更害怕爱上你
I'm afraid you're just fulfilling your original obsession
恐怕你只是在履行你最初的执念
But I have sincere feelings for you
但我对你有真挚的感情
thank you for everything you have done for me
谢谢你为我所做的一切
Guangxu's recall process is already underway.
光绪的召回程序已经在进行中。
Thanks
谢谢
Thank you for what?
谢谢你什么？
thank you for having them both
谢谢你让他们俩
the last time we met
我们最后一次见面
Actually I didn't expect
其实我没想到
You're actually helping the robot
你实际上是在帮助机器人
you misunderstood
你误会了
I am
我是
I help Jin Yan
我帮金妍
How is your recovery going?
你的康复进展如何？
beautiful
美好的
I've heard it all
我都听过
you did a great job
你做的非常出色
I didn’t expect this to be my first time taking charge
没想到这是我第一次负责
I encountered such a complicated situation
我遇到这么复杂的情况
But fortunately, it was resolved smoothly in the end.
不过还好最后顺利解决了
This is a very strange feeling
这是一种很奇怪的感觉
I always feel like it’s my own interference
总感觉是自己的干扰
Other people's lives are ruined
别人的生活被毁了
It's a hard balance to strike, isn't it?
很难取得平衡，不是吗？
let's get the point across
让我们明白重点
Do you have a premonition?
你有预感吗？
Is it a robot?
它是机器人吗？
Once determined
一旦确定
They must leave this society
他们必须脱离这个社会
That's all
仅此而已
This society can be more stable
这个社会才能更加稳定
this is work
这就是工作
the most painful place
最痛苦的地方
she
她
Why create robots
为什么要创造机器人
They say technology changes life
都说科技改变生活
But it ignores the complexity of human nature
但却忽视了人性的复杂性
stubborn
固执的
Now let the whole world pay the price
现在让全世界为此付出代价
What's up with her
她怎么了
I care about him very much
我很关心他
Why not come in and see for yourself?
为什么不亲自进来看看呢？
Isn't he awake?
他没醒吗？
What should I do?
我要做什么？
Was that fruit given to you by you?
那果子是你给的吧？
I found the address to buy Android
我找到了购买安卓的地址
Just on the old street
就在老街上
let's go
我们走吧
What are you doing standing there?
你站着做什么？
Don't want to go
不想去
he goes
他去
What's wrong
怎么了
are you here?
你在这儿吗？
Cheng Nu
程女
Lu Yan
卢燕